(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
3D LIVE 生演奏あり！
告知 & 新表情お披露目アリ！
3D LIVE with live music!
Announcements & new expression reveal!
FIRST STEP
HAKUI KOYORI BIRTHDAY LIVE 2025
博衣こより生誕Live2025
FIRST STEP
HAKUI KOYORI BIRTHDAY LIVE 2025
#HakuiKoyoriBirthdayLive2025
こんこよー！博衣こよりでーす！
Kon-koyo! I'm Hakui Koyori!
はい、ハッシュタグ 博衣こより生誕Live2025 でーす！
Yes, the hashtag is #HakuiKoyoriBirthdayLive2025!
おっけー、今夜はずーっと、ずーっと、盛り上がるよー！
Okay, tonight we're going to keep the excitement going on and on!
いよっしゃー！博衣こよりステージ、スタート！
Alright! The Hakui Koyori stage begins!
はい、お前ら！せーの！
Okay everyone! One, two!
ホイ！ホイ！ホイ！ホイ！
Hoi! Hoi! Hoi! Hoi!
勉強三昧 転換！
Transition from non-stop studying!
今宵の一地点 完！
Tonight's point, complete!
こよりの血色 満念！
Koyori's complexion, perfectly fulfilled!
今宵は ヘルプ！
Tonight, I need help!
うわー 一品目！
Whoa, the first dish!
助手くんなんで 見てて！
Because you're my assistants, watch me!
可愛いです 嫌！
It's cute, but no way!
おっけー、博衣こよりでーす！
Okay, I'm Hakui Koyori!
うわぁぁぁぁぁ！いよっしゃー、間に合ったー！
Whoaaa! Alright, I made it in time!
マヨネーズはお飲み物です。
Mayonnaise is a drink.
ちなみにスダチは空気です。
By the way, sudachi is air.
はい、お肉！点火！
Alright, meat! Fire it up!
冷凍うどんは常備してます。どうですか！？
I always have frozen udon in stock. How's that!?
よっしゃー！証明完了 Q.E.D.
Alright! Proof complete, Q.E.D.
ぼくらは博、博衣こより！
We are Hakui, Hakui Koyori!
こよりには コーヒーのびっくり
For Koyori, a coffee surprise!
いけるかな 無理無理無理無理
Can I do it? No way, no way, no way!
うりゃあ いきませんね
Hiyah! That won't do!
思いましょうわー！
Let's believe it, whoa!
ふわふわふわふわ 助けて！
Fluffy fluffy, save me!
はい、いーよ！おっけー！
Yes, good! Okay!
うぉぉぉぉ！いよっしゃー！
Whoooo! Alright!
いよっしゃー、間に合ったー！
Alright, I made it in time!
マヨネーズはお飲み物です。
Mayonnaise is a drink.
ちなみにスダチは空気です。
By the way, sudachi is air.
はい、お肉！点火！
Alright, meat! Fire it up!
冷凍うどんは常備してます。どうですか！？
I always have frozen udon in stock. How's that!?
よっしゃー！私の戦闘力、54万です！
Alright! My power level is 540,000!
実は私は17歳です！
Actually, I'm 17 years old!
アキレス腱に少々、そうだよ！
A little something for the Achilles tendon, that's right!
ハッシュタグで、パコパコ好き！
I love 'pakopako' in the hashtags!
うわぁ、150！150！
Whoa, 150! 150!
あむあむ、飲み物ではありません！
Nom nom, it's not a drink!
トンカツからあげ、イエス！
Tonkatsu, fried chicken, yes!
シッポもプッシュ、だめです！
Pushing the tail too, no way!
みんなの応援が一番だよ！
Everyone's support is the best!
右ってぇぇぇぇぇ！
To the right!
いよっしゃー、間に合ったー！
Alright, I made it in time!
マヨネーズはお飲み物です。
Mayonnaise is a drink.
ちなみにスダチは空気です。
By the way, sudachi is air.
はい、お肉！点火！
Alright, meat! Fire it up!
冷凍うどんは常備してます。どうですか！？
I always have frozen udon in stock. How's that!?
よっしゃー！せーの！
Alright! One, two!
こんこよー！
Kon-koyo!
こよりだよ！
I'm Koyori!
せーの！
Ready, set...
こんこよー！
Kon-koyo!
博衣こよりでーす！
I'm Hakui Koyori!
はい、ハッシュタグ 博衣こより生誕Live2025 でーす！
Yes, the hashtag is #HakuiKoyoriBirthdayLive2025!
おっけー、今夜はずーっと、ずーっと、盛り上がるよー！
Okay, tonight we're going to keep the excitement going on and on!
いよっしゃー！博衣こよりステージ、スタート！
Alright! The Hakui Koyori stage begins!
はい、お前ら！せーの！
Okay everyone! One, two!
ホイ！ホイ！ホイ！ホイ！
Hoi! Hoi! Hoi! Hoi!
勉強三昧、転換！
Transition from non-stop studying!
今宵の一地点、完！
Tonight's point, complete!
2025.03.15
HAKUI KOYORI
BIRTHDAY LIVE
FIRST STEP
博衣こより生誕Live 2025
Hakui Koyori Birthday Live 2025
もう キミの心 ちくっとしちゃえ
Now, I'll give your heart a little prick.
WAO!!
博衣こより生誕祭！
Hakui Koyori's Birthday Celebration!
1stアルバム発売記念ライブ！
1st Album Release Commemoration Live!
いっぱい盛り上がってこー！
Let's get super hyped!
絶対無理を むちゃしたって だって 不安になるし
Doing the impossible, overdoing it... it makes me anxious.
全然嘘つけないし だって どこまでも 真っ直ぐだし
I can't lie at all, because I'm straightforward to a fault.
まさかキラキラもきっと僕次第だ
The sparkle must depend on me too.
But don't give up なんて言わないんだから
I won't say 'don't give up' or anything.
じっとしてらんないし だって 動いちゃうし
I can't stay still, because I just have to move.
ワン、ツー、ステップ ちょっとずつ進めば
One, two, step, if I move forward bit by bit...
夢の指揮 溶けちゃうな
The boundaries of my dreams will melt away.
なりたい僕を 君が好きな僕を
The 'me' I want to be, the 'me' you like...
ちゃんと余りなく見せたいな
I want to show it all to you without holding back.
あっちゃっちゃ びっくりするほどできもんじゃん
Oh boy, I can do it surprisingly well!
間違って悩んだりバカじゃん
Making mistakes and worrying? That's silly!
けど君に見つけてほしくて
But I want you to find me.
僕は迎えに行くんだ だったらハッピー
So I'm coming to get you! That would be happy!
WAO!! WAO!! 叩け 手を
WAO!! WAO!! Clap your hands!
泣いて 笑って 愛して しっぽ振って
Cry, laugh, love, and wag your tail!
WAO!! WAO!! 叩け 手を
WAO!! WAO!! Clap your hands!
ダメな僕ごと覚えておいて
Remember me, even the bad parts.
もー キミの心 ちくっとしちゃえ
Now, I'll give your heart a little prick.
もー どうしようとか たまに思っちゃって沈んだり
Sometimes I wonder 'what should I do' and feel down.
案外いけるかも？ふわり 歌っちゃって また「どうも！」
Maybe I can actually do it? I sing lightly and say 'hello' again!
っぱり 読み切れない お座り 夢だっけ？
As expected, I can't quite figure it out. Was 'sit' just a dream?
うっかり 止められない また歩いて棒に当たるな
I carelessly can't stop, and I'll walk into a stick again.
ワン、ツー、ステップ 死んだフリしてるの？
One, two, step, are you playing dead?
やめて はい こっちおいで
Stop that, okay, come over here!
欲しがる君と あげすぎな僕とで
With the 'you' who wants, and the 'me' who gives too much...
もっといける気がしています
I feel like we can go even further.
あっちゃっちゃ びっくりするほどできもんじゃん
Oh boy, I can do it surprisingly well!
間違って悩んだりバカじゃん
Making mistakes and worrying? That's silly!
けど君に見つけてほしくて
But I want you to find me.
僕は迎えに行くんだ だったらハッピー
So I'm coming to get you! That would be happy!
だって やっぱり 一人じゃダメだけど
Because, as expected, I'm no good on my own.
集まって バカして わっちゃえば
But if we gather, act silly, and make some noise...
ほら いつでも言える「おかえり！」
Look, I can say 'welcome back' anytime!
僕は見せたいんだ 大いなるハッピー
I want to show you a great big 'happy'!
WAO!! WAO!! 叩け 手を
WAO!! WAO!! Clap your hands!
泣いて 笑って 愛して しっぽ振って
Cry, laugh, love, and wag your tail!
WAO!! WAO!! 叩け 手を
WAO!! WAO!! Clap your hands!
ダメな僕ごと覚えておいて
Remember me, even the bad parts.
まさかキラキラもきっと僕次第だ
The sparkle must depend on me too.
But don't give up なんて言わないんだから
I won't say 'don't give up' or anything.
刮目狙って ぶちかまし次第だ
I'll aim for your attention and give it my all!
はぐれずに希望へ 大爆走！
Galloping towards hope without getting lost!
君の心 ちくっとしちゃっていいじゃん ハッピーじゃん
It's okay if I prick your heart, isn't it? It's happy!
へへ、みんな、こんこよー！
Hehe, everyone, Kon-koyo!
ホロライブ6期生、秘密結社holoXの頭脳、博衣こよりだよー！
I'm the brains of Hololive Gen 6, Secret Society holoX, Hakui Koyori!
すごい躍っちゃった！
I danced so much!
ということで、みんな、こんこよー！
So, everyone, Kon-koyo!
博衣こより生誕ライブ2025にお越しくださいまして、ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming to Hakui Koyori Birthday Live 2025!
ということで、ここでみんなにめでたいことを2つ、お知らせさせていただきます！
So, I have two happy announcements for everyone!
まずは、博衣こより、誕生日を迎えましたー！
First, Hakui Koyori has reached her birthday!
わーい！わーい！わーい！
Yay! Yay! Yay!
や、めでたく無事に迎えることができました。
I was able to celebrate it safely.
みんな待っててくれてありがとう。
Thank you everyone for waiting.
そして、2つ目は、ファーストアルバムが発売になりましたー！
And the second one is, my first album has been released!
わーい！わーい！わーい！
Yay! Yay! Yay!
はい！ということでですね、本日はこのファーストアルバムをみんなにいっぱいお届けできるような、
Yes! And so, today, I wanted to create a "The Music Live" where I can deliver plenty
ザ・音楽ライブを作りたいと思いまして、中には生演奏コーナーもご用意してますよ！
from this first album to everyone, and we even have a live performance corner prepared!
生演奏、生出演していただきます。一緒に歌ってくださる、ミオ先輩もあっちの方で待ってます。
Participating in the live performance and appearing live... Mio-senpai, who will be singing with me, is waiting over there too.
控え室で待っていただいております。みお、みお、みおしゃの気配がしますね。はい、ということで。
She's waiting in the dressing room. I can feel Mio, Mio, Miosha's presence. Yes, so...
おめでとー！ありがとー！ まだ見えないです。そう、まだ見えないの。まだ待ってくれてます。
Congratulations! Thank you! You can't see her yet. Right, not yet. She's still waiting.
そしてですね、今回音楽ライブにするぞっていうので、ステージもなんかかっこよくしてもらいました！イエーイ！
And then, since we're making this a music live, the stage has been made really cool too! Yay!
こちらはですね、こよりらしく、インジウムって言うんですけど。ま、別に覚えなくていいんですけど。
This is, in a very Koyori-like way, called "Indium". Well, you don't really have to remember that.
ま、インジウムっていう化合物がね、あの浮んでいたりとかする巨大モニター。
Well, it's a giant monitor where Indium compounds are floating around.
なんとこのモニターですね、変形もしちゃうので、この後の曲も楽しみにしてください！
And surprisingly, this monitor even transforms, so please look forward to the songs coming up!
そして、すでにね、新表情ちょこちょこと出ております。この新表情もね、もうすごい、あの、ニュアンス変わってます、みたいな感じなんだけど、
Also, some new facial expressions have already been popping up here and there. These new expressions are like, "Wow, the nuance has changed!" and so on,
いっぱいパシャパシャとスクショ撮って、ハッシュタグ「#博衣こより生誕Live2025」でいっぱい呟いてください。
so please take lots of screenshots and tweet them with the hashtag #博衣こより生誕Live2025.
呟け！トレンド1位にしろー！ よろしくお願いします！
Tweet it! Make it trend #1! Thank you!
それでは、次の曲行っきまーす！
Alright, here we go with the next song!
デコレート / 作詞・作曲・編曲：かいりきベア
Decorate / Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Kairiki Bear
ヤ、ヘンな視線 いつだって 生態系
Ya, weird looks, always an ecosystem
艶めくの ノートへ お手、おて
Glossy, onto the notebook, paw, paw
あー 悠々自適 焦げ付いた 感触で
Ah, free and easy, with a scorched sensation
瞳の奥で イヤイヤイヤイヤ
In the depths of the eyes, no, no, no, no
ヤ、Falling Love 見つめ合っちゃってない？
Ya, Falling Love, aren't we staring at each other?
ピンク色 ハイライト 溶けて
Pink highlights melting
あー 糖分乱 はみ出た本能が
Ah, overflow, the protruding instinct
上手に隠しきら お待たせね
Can't hide it well, sorry to keep you waiting
シュッと ずっと シュッポッポ
Whoosh, always, chug-chug
いっぱい言いたいことあるでしょ
You have lots of things to say, right?
感情も着せ替えて
Changing the outfit of emotions too
カラフルに見せていいと
It's okay to show them colorfully
ラブリカッション ガチャメチャドッチャ
Love-rication, messily, clatteringly
リキったりして 奔放力
Straining, free-spirited power
キャピタリセセ 伸びしたり ぜんぜんぜん
Capitalize, stretching, not at all
デコレーション ガチャメチャドッチャ
Decoration, messily, clatteringly
デタラメ取り リズンダリ
Taking nonsense, distorted
ソレセイサイ ソレセイサイ
Sore-seisai, Sore-seisai
ソレセイサイ ゴナセ
Sore-seisai, gonna say
完璧な笑顔で お代わり
With a perfect smile, "Another helping, please!"
最近の ネガティブなスパイク
Recent negative spikes
ポジティブ アイシャドウ 待って待って
Positive eyeshadow, wait, wait
Falling Love 見つめ合っちゃってない？
Falling Love, aren't we staring at each other?
ピンク色 ナメック お待たせね
Pinkish... sorry to keep you waiting
はい！デコレーション / せーの！デコレーション
Yes! Decoration / Ready, set, go! Decoration
誰もこれも私
Everyone, everything is me
感情も着せ替えて
Changing the outfit of emotions too
カラフルなスクランブル
A colorful scramble
ラブリカッション ガチャメチャドッチャ
Love-rication, messily, clatteringly
リキったりして 奔放力
Straining, free-spirited power
キャピタリセセ 猟奇的ない ぜんぜんぜん
Capitalize, not bizarre at all
ラブリカッション ガチャメチャドッチャ
Love-rication, messily, clatteringly
デタラメ取り リズンダリ
Taking nonsense, distorted
ソレセイサイ ソレセイサイ
Sore-seisai, Sore-seisai
ソレセイサイ ゴナセ
Sore-seisai, gonna say
完璧な笑顔で お代わり
With a perfect smile, "Another helping, please!"
粛聖!! ロリ神レクイエム☆ / 作詞：まろん (IOSYS) 作曲：D.Watt (IOSYS)
Shukusei!! Loli-Kami Requiem☆ / Lyrics: Maron (IOSYS), Composition: D.Watt (IOSYS)
なに、なに、なにかみかみ、
What, what, what-kami-kami,
金を鳴らせばこの通り。
Ring the bell, and just like this.
これは救済の
This is a requiem
レクイエム
of salvation
せーの！
Ready, set, go!
触ったら逮捕！
Touch me and you're arrested!
極Chuで逮捕！
Arrested for your extreme creepiness!
いちにーさんしー？
One, two, three, four?
ごめんねさーい
I'm sowwy!
「ごめんねさーい」が聞こえない
I can't hear your "I'm sowwy"!
粛聖！！ロリ神レクイエム☆
Judgment!! Loli-God Requiem☆
将来はお前なんかに好かれたくない
I don't want to be liked by someone like you in the future.
泥水で口を洗え
Wash your mouth out with muddy water.
法廷で会おう？
See you in court, okay?
ねえ、おまわりさん連れて行って
Hey, officer, take this person away.
妄想しか取り柄のない可哀想な人
Such a pitiful person with nothing going for them but delusions.
（ういちゃん！ういちゃん！待ってよ、ういちゃん！）
(Ui-chan! Ui-chan! Wait up, Ui-chan!)
その姿、親に見せられますかぁ？
Can you actually show yourself like that to your parents?
（こよちゃん！こよちゃん！かわいいよぉ〜！）
(Koyo-chan! Koyo-chan! You're so cute!)
ねえ、ありがとう。お疲れ様です〜
Hey, thanks. Thanks for your hard work~
ロリより神降臨　マジやば奴等に用心
The Loli-God descends, beware of the truly dangerous creeps.
まともじゃないなら　早く消えてください
If you're not sane, please disappear quickly.
Lovely ロリロリ神降臨　鐘を鳴らせばこの通り
Lovely, the Loli-God descends; ring the bell and look here.
とても優しくて　素敵なお兄ちゃん
A very kind and wonderful big brother.
楽園でほら　ねんねしな
Now, go to sleep in paradise.
ほら、世の中にはこんなに気持ち悪い人たちがはびこっているんです
Look, the world is crawling with disgusting people like this.
みんな晒し上げますよ？
I'm going to expose all of you, okay?
触ったら逮捕！
Touch me and you're arrested!
極Chuで逮捕！
Arrested for your extreme creepiness!
いちにーさんしー？
One, two, three, four?
ごめんねさーい
I'm sowwy!
「ごめんねさーい」が聞こえない
I can't hear your "I'm sowwy"!
粛聖！！ロリ神レクイエム☆
Judgment!! Loli-God Requiem☆
はーい、獄中にいる皆さーん、刑務所ファンミーティングのお時間でーす！
Okay, everyone in prison! It's time for the prison fan meeting!
その、腐りきった耳をゴリゴリかっぽじって、よく聴いてくださいね？
Scrub those rotten ears out and listen closely, okay?
（助かる〜）キモキモ（助かる〜）うるさい
(I'm saved~) Gross (I'm saved~) Shut up.
（助かる〜）黙ってもらっていいですか？（助かる〜）嫌いです
(I'm saved~) Could you please just shut up? (I'm saved~) I hate you.
（助かる〜）かわいそう（助かる〜）だーさーい
(I'm saved~) Pitiful (I'm saved~) Lame.
よーわーい　みっともなーい！
Weak. Pathetic!
どうしようもない　お兄ちゃんお姉ちゃん
Hopeless big brothers and big sisters.
もう希望もない　ゴミだおめーら
No more hope, you're all just trash.
汚物消毒　110番
Sanitizing filth, calling 110.
固有結界　は・つ・ど・う　粛聖！
Reality Marble activation: Judgment!
ういビーム！！
Ui-beam!!
もういっちょ！ういビーム！！
One more! Ui-beam!!
怒りの日。聖なるインターネットに、血の雨が降り注いだ日。
Dies Irae. The day a rain of blood poured down upon the holy internet.
愚かなロリコンを骨の髄まで浄化する、一筋の光。
A single ray of light to purify the foolish lolicons to their very marrow.
それが、ういビームなのである。ういは全てを許します。
That is the Ui-beam. Ui forgives everything.
嗚呼　この世の醜さを　集めて描いてみるよ
Ah, I'll gather and depict the ugliness of this world.
真っ白なキャンバスが　汚れて泣いている
The pure white canvas is crying, stained with filth.
ふと振り向いた少女は　そっと手を掴む
The girl who suddenly turned around softly takes your hand.
「楽園など無いから」
"Because there is no paradise."
おっきなお友達の皆え、お前らが打ち込んでいる曲には、何の味があるの？
To all our big "friends": What meaning is there in the song you're so into?
ねえ、教えてよ。こよ、ぜんぜーんわかんないんだ！
Hey, tell me. Koyo doesn't understand at all!
ロリより神降臨　さよなら笑顔でバイバイ
The Loli-God descends, goodbye with a smile, bye-bye.
ピリオドをどうぞ　この手で押してあげゆ
Here's your period, I'll press it for you with this hand.
Lovely ロリロリ神降臨　鐘を鳴らせばこの通り
Lovely, the Loli-God descends; ring the bell and look here.
とても優しくて　素敵なお兄ちゃん
A very kind and wonderful big brother.
楽園でほら　ねんねしな
Now, go to sleep in paradise.
それが救済の　レクイエム
That is the requiem of salvation.
せーのっ
One, two!
触ったら逮捕！
Touch me and you're arrested!
極Chuで逮捕！
Arrested for your extreme creepiness!
いちにーさんしー？
One, two, three, four?
ごめんねさーい
I'm sowwy!
「ごめんねさーい」が聞こえない
I can't hear your "I'm sowwy"!
粛聖！！ロリ神レクイエム☆
Judgment!! Loli-God Requiem☆
ほんっとーに、気持ち悪い。
You're really, truly disgusting.
う、ういちゃーん！
U-Ui-chan!
こわっ
Scary
ういちゃーん！
Ui-chan!
誰？
Who are you?
可愛いよー！えへへ
You're so cute! Ehehe
だから誰？
I said, who are you?
こよりお姉ちゃんだよ！
It's Big Sister Koyori!
あ、どうも。さよなら。
Ah, hello. Goodbye.
あ、ちょっと待ってちょっと待って！
Ah, wait a second, wait a second!
ういビーム、出てる？
Is the Ui-beam coming out?
出てないです、さようなら。
No it's not, goodbye.
あー！もう一回、もう一回！
Ah! One more time, one more time!
なんですか？
What is it?
体操座りで見てもらえる？
Can you watch me while sitting with your knees up?
やば、不審者だ。
Wow, a suspicious person.
ういちゃーん！
Ui-chan!
この後、お姉ちゃんちに来てほしかった...
I wanted you to come to Big Sister's house after this...
お誕生日プレゼントにういちゃんもらえるんじゃないのー？
Can't I get Ui-chan as a birthday present?
おうちに持ち帰っていいんじゃないのー！？
Can't I take her home!?
うわあああああ！
Uwaaaaa!
うわあ...
Uwaa...
ういママ先生、何してんの？
Ui-mama sensei, what are you doing?
あれ？さっきまでロリじゃなかったですか？
Huh? Weren't you a loli until just now?
いやいやいやいや...私が...
No, no, no, no... I was...
今、今すれ違わなかったですか？可愛い...
Didn't we just pass each other? Cute...
え、待って待って、誰誰？知らない知らない。
Wait, wait, who are you? I don't know you.
知らない？誰はおかしいですよ！
You don't know me? 'Who' is a strange thing to say!
いや、誰？怖い。あなたの幼少期でしょう？
No, really, who? This is scary. I'm you in your childhood, right?
いやいやいやいや！
No way, no way, no way!
え、てか何？何その姿は。
Wait, what's with that look?
あ、今話してる？ロリ神...
Ah, are you talking about it now? Loli-gami...
ロリ神！やってるじゃないですか！そーねー。
Loli-gami! You're doing it! Yeah...
え、恥ずかしいよ。
It's embarrassing.
え、え？こんなことしてる、恥ずかしい。
What am I doing? It's embarrassing.
あれ？自分だってつけてた。
Wait, I was wearing it myself.
え、なに？これ？外してくるから。
What? This? I'll go take it off.
あ、あ、はい。
Ah, okay.
あれ？記憶これ共有されないタイプなのか？
Wait, is this the kind of memory that isn't shared?
え、なに、何言ってんだろう。
What... what is she saying?
え、お一人になっちゃった。
Eh, I'm all alone.
みんな、こんにちは！私が乗っ取ったよ！
Everyone, hello! I've taken over!
乗っ取ったよ！
I took over!
乗っ取ってない！
You didn't take over!
ただいま戻りましたよ！
I'm back!
こよちゃん、ちょっと衝撃映像見てたから忘れちゃってたけど...
Koyo-chan, I was watching that shocking footage so I almost forgot...
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
あ、やったー！ありがとうございます！
Ah, yay! Thank you so much!
おめでとうございます、誕生日ガール！
Congratulations, birthday girl!
誕生日ガール！大丈夫？一人ずつ喋って。
Birthday girl! Are you okay? Speak one at a time.
いやいや、怖すぎる！一人じゃないよ！
No, no, it's too scary! I'm not alone!
いたんだよ、さっきまでロリういちゃんが！
Loli-Ui-chan was here until just now!
幻みたいな...
Like a phantom...
ロリういちゃんはいるんだ！
Loli-Ui-chan is here!
そっか。
I see.
いたもん！
She was here!
そっか。じゃあ、なんかしてたの？さっき二人で。
I see. So, were you two doing something just now?
そうなんです。いおすさんの作ったね、
That's right! We were...
メメメクイーンを一緒に歌って踊っていたわけですよ。
singing and dancing to 'Meme-Meme Queen' made by Ios-san.
そうなんだ。私とは何もしてくれないってわけ？
I see. So you won't do anything with me?
え？え？え？したけど？
Eh? Eh? Eh? But we did...
え、や、してない。してない。まだ何もしてない、まだ。
No, wait, we haven't. Not yet. We haven't done anything yet.
でも、でも、でも！それは、歌って踊ってくれるってこと？
But, but, but! Does that mean you'll sing and dance with me?
もち、なんのために来たと思ってんだ！
Of course! What do you think I came here for?
やったー！もう一曲やってくれるんだ、嬉しい！
Yay! She's going to do another song with me! I'm so happy!
一曲...いや、まだ一曲しかやってない。
One song... well, we've only done one song so far.
ややこしいな！ややこしいな。
How confusing! So confusing.
え、え、じゃあなんですけど、あの、この前ね、
Well then, the other day...
こよりが行きそびれてしまった凸待ちの時に...
during the call-in stream that Koyori missed...
こう、こよちゃんの新曲、結構聞いててってお話ししてくれてたじゃないですか。
you said you'd been listening to my new song a lot, right?
オタクの配信見ないで！
Don't watch the otaku streams!
アーカイブ全部見た！最初から最後まで見たから！やだー。
I watched the whole archive! From start to finish! Oh no.
じゃあ、あの曲！あの曲、お願いしてもいいですか？
Then, that song! Could I ask you for that song?
歌っていただいてもいいんですか？
Would you sing it with me?
もちろんですよ！ああ、いいや、もうやる気満々じゃないな。
Of course! Ah, wait, I'm already all fired up.
練習しましたからね、一緒にやったもんね。
I practiced for it, we did it together.
ね、やりましたね。頑張った！
We did! We worked hard!
はい！ということでね、こちら、まらんさんにも手掛けていただいた楽曲...
Okay! So, this song, which was also worked on by Maran-san...
『シアワセ☆コヨリニウム』、一緒に歌って踊っちゃいます！
'Shiawase Korononium'! We're going to sing and dance it together!
イェーイ！
Yay!
じゃあスタンバイ、スタンバイしましょう。やるぞ、やるぞ、やるぞ！
Let's get ready! Let's do it, let's do it, let's do it!
コヨチャン チュキチュキ！
Koyo-chan, chuki chuki!
えへへ、えへへ！
Ehehe, ehehe!
みんなの脳みそに...
In everyone's brains...
お注射しちゃうぞ！
I'm gonna give an injection!
実験！実験！実験だ！
Experiment! Experiment! It's an experiment!
（うわ～～かっぷー！）
(Uwaa~ Kappu!)
実験！実験！実験だ！実験だ！
Experiment! Experiment! It's an experiment! It's an experiment!
研究 研究 研究！IQ 快求上昇中！
Research, research, research! IQ is rising!
呼ばれて 飛び出て パピプペポ BOOM!
Called out and popped out, Papipupepo BOOM!
継承 継承 継承！CAUTION アテンションプリーズ！
Attention, attention! Caution, Attention please!
なめてたら発火しちゃうよ！
If you lick it, I'll ignite it!
（マヨ！）
(Mayo!)
迷っちゃダメダメ 真夜中サイエンス
Don't, don't, Midnight Science!
魔除けの呪文は マヨマヨちゅっちゅ！
The spell of protection is Mayo Mayo Chucchu!
（こよ！）
(Koyo!)
今宵は1時過ぎ 高揚するHeart Beat
At night, after 1:00 AM, high-speed Heart Beat!
コヨコヨいなれ こいこがれ～
Koyokoyo, be in love, be in love!
（かっぷー）
(Kappu!)
サイン コサイン タンジェント (Ay!)
Sine, Cosine, Tangent! (Ay!)
試験管 → Docking → Direct!
Test tube → Docking → Direct!
白衣の天使が降臨！
The white-clad angel descends!
天才 天才 天才！とんでもなく偉い！
Genius, genius, genius! Incredibly great!
崇めちゃってOK (OK!)
It's okay to worship! (OK!)
褒めてくスタイル
The praising style!
最高 最高 最高！そんでラブって優勝
Best, best, best! Then love and win!
ぶっちゃけ脳内シュワシュワ スタンディングオベーション！
Actually, brain is bubbling, Standing Ovation!
(Wow-o-o-o)
科学とは...爆発だ！
Science is... an explosion!
ポチッとピポパ 間違えてドッカーン
Pochi-tto Pipopa, mistake and Dokkaan!
ドジなトコも 計算通りよ
Even the clumsy parts are as calculated!
実験！実験！実験だ！
Experiment! Experiment! It's an experiment!
（うわ～～かっぷー！）
(Uwaa~ Kappu!)
実験！実験！実験だ！実験だ！
Experiment! Experiment! It's an experiment! It's an experiment!
さあ～て、早速始めましょう！
Well then, let's start quickly!
これよりお送りするのは、天才マッドサイエンティストと...
This time it's by the genius mad scientist and...
天才イラストレーターによる...
...the genius illustrator!
世にも奇妙な、すん～ばらしい大～実験！
A strange and wonderful grand experiment!
ようこそ魅惑のラボラトリー (ドキドキワクワク 胸打つ鼓動)
Welcome to the enchanting laboratory! (Doki-doki heart pounding)
怖くない 大丈夫よ (ホラケタケタカラカラ 笑いましょう)
It's not scary, it's okay. (Hora keta keta, let's laugh)
試験管をブッ刺せば完了 (ドクドクバクバク 胸打つ鼓動)
It's complete if you stick the test tube in! (Doku doku heart pounding)
「原子番号315番、コヨリニウム。
"Atomic number 315, Koronium.
これは、シアワセになる、最高の粒子なのかな？」
Is this the best particle to become happy?"
病みつきになっちゃえばEジャン
It's fine if you get addicted!
欲しいなら叫べばEジャン
It's fine if you shout if you want it!
大好きですか？（大好きでーす！）
Do you love me? (I love you!)
シアワセですか？（シアワセでーす！）
Are you happy? (I'm happy!)
愛すれば救われる。あ、なんて素敵な世界なんでしょう。 「ほんまか？」
If you love, you'll be saved. Ah, what a wonderful world it is. "Is that true?"
一途なその瞳で...
With those devoted eyes...
一途なその瞳で
With those devoted eyes
見つめて！
Stare at me!
推して！萌えて！溶けちゃえ！
Support me! Adore me! Melt away!
Yeah!
明るい未来に乾杯！
Cheers to a bright future!
天才！天才！天才！
Genius! Genius! Genius!
ハチャメチャにすごい
Incredibly amazing
祀られてOK！
Being worshiped is OK!
神ってるスタイル
God-like style
最高！最高！最高！
The best! The best! The best!
呼ばれたらずっと
If called, always
本気で脳髄トロトロスタンディングオベーション
Seriously, brain marrow melting standing ovation
人生とは...
Life is...
爆発さ！
An explosion!
ポチっとピポパ
Click and beep-boop-beep
やっぱりまたドッカーン！
As expected, another boom!
どんなトコも計算通り
Everywhere is just as calculated
（計算通り）
(Just as calculated)
計算通りよ！
It's just as calculated!
実験だ！実験だ！
It's an experiment! It's an experiment!
実験！実験！実験だ！
Experiment! Experiment! It's an experiment!
実験だ！実験だ！
It's an experiment! It's an experiment!
う、う、う〜〜〜カッポ！
U, u, u~~~ Kapo!
実験だ！実験だ！
It's an experiment! It's an experiment!
実験！実験！実験だ！
Experiment! Experiment! It's an experiment!
実験だ！実験だ！
It's an experiment! It's an experiment!
実・験・だ〜〜！
Ex-per-i-ment~~!
実験だ〜〜！
It's an experiment~~!
ミャーオ！
Meow!
ねえねえ私気づいてる
Hey, hey, I've noticed
見えるように消しゴム落としたり
You dropping your eraser so I can see
教科書だって実は忘れてない
You didn't actually forget your textbook
バレて慌ててる君は猫みたい
You, panicked after being caught, are like a cat
「全然勉強してねーわー」
"I'm not studying at all"
「あんなん俺でも出来ちゃうわー」
"I could do that too"
男子ってば単純ね
Boys are so simple
愛想笑いでハイハイね
Smiling politely, yeah, yeah
変な髪型
What a weird hairstyle
それ言うな
Don't say that
いちいち虫とか見せんでいい！
You don't need to show me bugs every time!
そうやって気を引くのなんとかなんないの？
Can't you do something about the way you try to get attention?
もう遊ぶ気分じゃなくなっちゃうかもダーリン
I might not feel like playing anymore, darling
カッコつけさせてあげるから
I'll let you act cool
キメてよね
So strike a pose
（にゃっ！）
(Nyah!)
コネコミュニケーション
Konecommunication
噛みついちゃう予感
A feeling I'll bite
合図だぞ！見逃せない
It's a signal! Can't miss it
（ミャオ！）
(Meow!)
コネコミュニケーション
Konecommunication
からかうだけじゃわっかんない！
I won't understand if you're just teasing!
聴かせてよ
Let me hear it
（ミャオ！）
(Meow!)
飛び込んじゃお
Let's dive in
爪立てちゃお
Let's show our claws
時々は撫でられたい？
Do you want to be petted sometimes?
きっと手のひら一杯愛で
Surely with a handful of love
気まぐれを仕留めて！
Capture my whims!
ミャオ
Meow
興味ないって言いながらこっち見てる
Saying you're not interested while looking this way
聞こえるように好きな子の話してる
Talking about the girl you like so I can hear
他の子と仲良しで照れ隠し
Hiding your shyness by being friendly with other girls
聞き耳立てちゃうよねバカみたい！
I'm straining to hear, how stupid!
「絆創膏とかいらねーわー」
"I don't need a band-aid"
「本気でやったら勝ってたわー」
"If I'd been serious, I would've won"
そーなんだすっごいね
Is that so, how amazing
じゃあ最初からやっとけば？
Then why didn't you do it from the start?
「あいつ、お前が好きだって絶対誰にも言うなって！」
"That guy, don't you ever tell anyone he likes you!"
そーなんだ気になっちゃう付き合っちゃおっかな？
Is that so, now I'm curious, maybe I should date him?
ねえ殻を破った君も素敵よダーリン
Hey, you're wonderful even when you break out of your shell, darling
溜め息だって駆け引きね
Even a sigh is a tactic
数えてて
Keep counting them
（にゃっ！）
(Nyah!)
コネコミュニケーション
Konecommunication
ためらっちゃうボタン
The button that makes me hesitate
本気だぞ！強がりたい
I'm serious! I want to act tough
（ミャオ！）
(Meow!)
コネコミュニケーション
Konecommunication
じゃれ合うたびにわっかんない！
Every time we play together, I just don't get it!
教えてよ
Tell me
（ミャオ！）
(Meow!)
落ち込んじゃお
Let's get depressed
背伸びしちゃお
Let's stretch ourselves
よしよし甘えられない？
There, there, can't you be a bit spoiled?
嫉妬猫（ジェラシーキャット）みたい言っちゃいたいね
I want to say I'm like a jealous cat
熱いのは苦手よ！
I'm not good with hot things!
ミャオ
Meow
もう！なんでもないわ聞き飽きちゃったよダーリン
Enough! It's nothing, I'm tired of hearing it, darling
目配せなんてとっておきも
Even that special wink
君にだけ
Only for you
（みやっ）
(Miyah)
コネコミュニケーション
Konecommunication
噛みついちゃう予感
A feeling I'll bite
合図だぞ！見逃せない
It's a signal! Can't miss it
（ミャオ！）
(Meow!)
コネコミュニケーション
Konecommunication
からかうだけじゃわっかんない！
I won't understand if you're just teasing!
聴かせてよ
Let me hear it
（ミャオ！）
(Meow!)
飛び込んじゃお
Let's dive in
爪立てちゃお
Let's show our claws
ドキドキ離れられない？
Heart pounding, can't get away?
尻尾振るように頂戴愛
Give me love like wagging a tail
そっぽ向きがち曖昧じゃ
Being vague and looking away
やっぱ君にはもったいないね
As expected, it's too good for you
気が向けばあげるわ！
I'll give it to you if I feel like it!
チャオ☆
Ciao☆
ねーねー！
Nene-ne!
よーこそー！
Welcome!
イェーイ！
Yay!
誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
ありがとうございまーす！
Thank you very much!
来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming!
こちらこそ呼んでくれてありがとう！
Thank you for inviting me!
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
ということで元気に飛び...
And with that, let's energetically...
ゲストに来ていただきました！
We have a guest here with us today!
去年の5月にコラボしたぶり、P丸様。ことぴーちゃんです！
Our first collab since last May—it's P-maru-sama, aka P-chan!
イエーイ！！アハハハ！
Yeeeah!! Ahahaha!
おたけびかｗ
What a roar lol
イエーイ！イエーイ！センキュー！
Yeeeah! Yeeeah! Thank you!
ということでね、今歌わせていただいたのは
So, the song we just performed was
ぴーちゃんの新曲「ななほし管弦楽団さんのだよね」
P-chan's new song, Nanahoshi Kangengaku-dan's 'Dayone',
そうなんですよねー！一緒に歌わせていただきました！
That's right! We sang it together!
ワーイ！可愛かったー！
Yay! That was so cute!
可愛かったー！イェーイ！
It was cute! Yay!
嬉しい！こんな感じでね、ちょっとテンション高く始めたんですけど
I'm so happy! We started off with a lot of energy like this,
実はですね、こより…何笑ってんだよｗ
but actually, Koyori... what are you laughing at? lol
実はあのぴーちゃんに言いたいことが一つあるんです
Actually, there's one thing I wanted to say to P-chan.
はい、何だろう？
Yes, what is it?
あのー前にね、ぴーちゃんが…近いｗ
Um, so a while back, P-chan... too close! lol
なになに？ぴーちゃんがね、去年の末ぐらいに
What is it? Around the end of last year, P-chan,
「今年懺悔したいこと」っていうのを配信で喋ってたんですよ
you were talking about 'Things I want to repent for this year' on stream.
あー、うんうん
Ah, right, right.
その時にね、「こよりちゃんのことを猫だと思ってたんだけど」
At that time, you said, 'I used to think Koyori-chan was a cat,'
「ごめんなさい、狐だったんだね」って言ってたんですよ！
'but I'm sorry, you were actually a fox!'
え、待って、狐じゃないの？
Wait, hold on, you're not a fox?
コヨーテだよ！
I'm a coyote!
コヨーテって何？え、コヨーテって狐の妖怪じゃないの？
What's a coyote? Wait, isn't a coyote a fox spirit?
え、なんでｗ
Wait, why? lol
狐の妖怪は「妖狐（ようこ）」やろ！
The fox spirit is 'Yoko'!
あー、そっか！え、妖狐、妖狐、妖狐、コヨーテ、ってこと？
Oh, I see! So it's Yoko, Yoko, Yoko, coyote?
そうそうそう、じゃないんだよ！ｗ
Exactly! ...Wait, no it's not! lol
じゃあコヨーテって何？
Then what is a coyote?
コヨーテはコヨーテや！こよりのことや！
A coyote is a coyote! It's me, Koyori!
ヤバーイ！ｗ
Oh man! lol
「オオカミ、キツネ、コヨーテ」みたいな感じで種類がありますんで
It's a type, like 'Wolf, Fox, Coyote.'
今日だけはね、今日はこれを覚えて帰っていただければと思っております
I hope you can at least remember that before you go home today.
わかった！よかったー！
Understood! Good to know!
はい！ということでですね、そんなぴーちゃんと
Alright! So, with P-chan here,
前にコラボした時に「一緒に歌いたいね」って言ってた歌があるんですよね
there's a song we said we wanted to sing together back when we collaborated.
そう！イエーイ！
Yes! Yeeeah!
はい、そのね曲を、この後もう一曲一緒に歌っちゃいたいと思います！
We're going to sing that song together right now!
ワーイ！ワーイ！じゃあせっかくなんでこより、万歳してくんね？
Yay! Yay! Well then, Koyori, why don't you do a 'Banzai' for us?
万歳！万歳！万歳！万歳！
Banzai! Banzai! Banzai! Banzai!
万歳！えっ、それ何のポーズやろｗ
Banzai! Wait, what's that pose? lol
可愛い！可愛いですよ！
It's cute! You look cute!
ありがとうございます！ハイ！
Thank you! Alright!
ちょっとね、白衣っぽい上着を着まして、
I've put on a lab-coat-like jacket,
次に歌うのは同じななほし管弦楽団さんのね、
and the next song is also by Nanahoshi Kangengaku-dan.
曲、一緒に歌いましょう！
Let's sing it together!
やったー！やったー！歌おう！歌おう！
Hooray! Hooray! Let's sing! Let's sing!
それでは、聴いてください！
Now, please listen!
せーの！乙女よ求めよQ.E.D.！！
One, two! Otome yo Motome yo Q.E.D.!!
何笑ってんねんｗ
What are you laughing at? lol
乙女よ求めよQ.E.D.！！
Otome yo Motome yo Q.E.D.!!
Question! 知りたいな
Question! I want to know
君はさ 僕のこと どう思う？
What do you think of me?
Question! 僕はね 君のこと……
Question! As for me, about you...
あとは宿題
The rest is homework
ラブ・ラボ 引きこもっちゃうな？
Love-Lab, will you shut yourself in?
聞かなきゃって…ほら相性！
I have to ask... look, our compatibility!
論より証拠主義です
Proof over argument is my policy
前進あるのみ！
Only moving forward!
ねえ。少し手伝って
Hey. Help me out a bit
人類の課題
A challenge for humanity
好き×好き×好き×好き＝？
Like x like x like x like = ?
答え合わせしましょ？
Shall we check the answer?
見つけちゃう 魔法の公式
I'll find it, the magic formula
化学反応 してるよね
We're having a chemical reaction, aren't we?
僕ら 問題は
Our problem is
まだまだまだまだ未解決
Still, still, still, still unsolved
証明中 恋の予想
Proving our love's hypothesis
物理法則 書き出しちゃうもんね
I'll write out the physical laws
これぞ天才だ！
This is a genius!
あの子より その子より
More than that girl, more than her,
もっと大好きって言って頂だい
Tell me that you love me even more
乙女よ 求めよ Q.E.D.！！
Otome yo Motome yo Q.E.D.!!
Question!!
やっぱりさ さっきから
I knew it, for a while now,
僕のこと……見てたよね？
You've been... looking at me, haven't you?
Question!! 見てない？
Question!! You weren't?
じゃあ……僕が 君のこと
Then... I'll be the one looking at you
どぎまぎパラドックス
A flustered paradox
慌てちゃって隠れちゃう？
Getting panicked and hiding away?
宇宙も秘密主義じゃ
If even the universe is secretive,
ビッグバン！
Big Bang!
ねえ。君とふたり
Hey. Just the two of us
人類の終わり
The end of humanity
好き×好き×好き×好き
Like x like x like x like
無限大未来でしょ？
It's an infinite future, right?
解きましょ 魔法の公式
Let's solve it, the magic formula
惹かれ合うたび 不思議な
Every time we're attracted, a mysterious
レポートは
Report is
まだまだまだまだ未提出
Still, still, still, still unsubmitted
設計中 DNA
Designing DNA
君の細胞 書き換えちゃうもんね
I'll rewrite your cells
ズバリ天才だ！
In short, a genius!
どの子より この子より
More than any girl, more than this one,
ずっと好きって言ってるじゃん！
I've been saying I love you forever!
乙女よ 急げよ Q.E.D.！！
Otome yo Isoge yo Q.E.D.!!
乙女よ求めよQ.E.D.
O Maiden, Seek Q.E.D.
好き×好き×好き×好き×好き×好き＝？
Love x Love x Love x Love x Love x Love = ?
ねえ。僕らふたり 人類の終わりに
Hey. The two of us, at the end of humanity,
割り切れなかったあまりだったら
If we were the remainder that couldn't be divided out...
ねえ。少し手伝って
Hey. Help me out a little
人類の課題
With humanity's challenge.
好き×好き×好き×好き×好き×好き
Love x Love x Love x Love x Love x Love,
答え合わせしましょう？
Shall we check our answers?
見つけちゃう！ 魔法の公式
I'll find it! The magic formula.
化学反応してるよね
A chemical reaction is happening, right?
僕ら問題は
Our problem is
まだまだまだまだ未解決
Still, still, still, still unsolved.
証明中 恋の予想
Currently proving the hypothesis of love.
物理法則 書き足しちゃうもんね
I'll even add to the laws of physics!
これぞ天才だ！
This is what a genius is!
あの子より この子より
More than that girl, more than this girl,
もっと（好きって）言ってちょうだい
Please say (you love me) even more!
乙女よ乙女よ Q.E.D.!
O maidens, O maidens, Q.E.D.!
(3.14)
(3.14159265358979323846264338327...)
Q.E.D.!!
今、以上、最大。
Now, more than ever, the greatest.
叶えましょう！
Let's make it come true!
みんな楽しんでる？
Is everyone having fun?
ここからはオリ曲メドレー！
From here on, it's an original song medley!
史上最大のQUESTION!
The Greatest QUESTION in History!
行くよ！
Here we go!
究極新時代 メラメラ抑えられないのです。
A new ultimate era, I can't suppress this flare-up.
レギュラなので余裕です。
I'm a regular, so it's a breeze.
今夜は頭脳で素直。
Tonight, I'll be honest with my brains.
またひとつ発見
Another discovery:
マヨネーズは飲み物です。
Mayonnaise is a drink.
カモン Q & A
Come on, Q & A!
あっちこっち ほら巻き起こる
Look, it's breaking out here and there,
ドラマに体当たり
Crashing headfirst into drama.
次元感じてみなきゃ始まらない
It won't start until you try to feel the dimensions.
研究 精製 共有
Research, refine, share.
DEAR YOU, ARE YOU OK?
一緒にドンドン過ごしましょう
Let's spend more and more time together.
あなたと経験していこう タイム
Let's gain experiences with you, time!
全部の夢 その手で Q.E.D.
All your dreams, in those hands, Q.E.D.
仕掛けはまた次がある
There's always another trick up my sleeve.
泣いて笑って WOW
Crying and laughing, WOW!
どんな日も永遠 願わす MY
I wish for eternity, every day, MY...
その胸に芽生えてほしい幸せ
I want happiness to sprout in that heart of yours.
今、以上、最大。叶えましょう！
Now, more than ever, the greatest. Let's make it come true!
アンバランス
Unbalance
難解すぎる愛の方程式
The formula for love is too complex.
教えて曖昧な答えだす必要はない
Tell me, there's no need to give a vague answer.
未経験的な性質だって
Even with unexperienced qualities,
不安定も歓迎 片足で立って
Instability is welcome too, standing on one leg...
支えていてよ
Keep supporting me!
僕の正体
My true identity...
アンバランスな
Unbalanced,
僕の証明
My proof.
New Journey
始めよう。正義を共に掲げれば
Let's begin. If we hold up justice together,
思い通りの光が
The light just as we imagined
今すぐ飛び出していく
Will fly out right now.
羽ばたいた
I spread my wings.
忘れないでね この眩しさを
Don't forget this radiance.
希望に満ちた輝き 追いかけて
Chasing the brilliance full of hope,
あり得ない景色に
Towards an impossible landscape,
辿り着きましょう
Let's reach it.
エゴイスティック・シーソー
Egoistic Seesaw
招待 頂戴
Invitation, please!
一緒に楽しもうよ
Let's have fun together!
シーソー 壊すほど目一杯 戯れて
Frolicking so hard on the seesaw that it breaks,
居場所を記した
Marking our place.
星屑は日常 何でしょう
Stardust is everyday life, I wonder what it is.
後悔のないよう 最後まで
Until the end, so there are no regrets,
生き急ごう
Let's live life in the fast lane.
やりたいこと成して 楽しく
Doing what we want to do and having fun.
手を振って私でいたい 苦しいなんて
Waving my hand, I want to be myself. Don't tell me it's painful,
やだわ
I hate that!
ワガママな夢 もっと 謳歌しよう
Let's enjoy our selfish dreams even more!
Tear-Gazer
行くよ！
Here we go!
…は 君の前で
...before you,
笑ってみせる
I'll show you a smile.
強がりの僕らだけど
Though we both try to act tough,
毛布の中一人で
Alone under the blankets,
涙流す日もある
There are days when we shed tears.
孤独の旋律さ
It's a melody of loneliness.
自分に正直な
Being honest with myself,
やりたいにまっすぐな
Following my desires directly,
君だけのヒーローで ありたい
I want to be your very own hero.
悔しさを重ねて
Accumulating my regrets,
駆け上がっていこうぜ
Let's run up to the top!
今はまだ未知の途中
We're still in the middle of the unknown.
きっと...
Surely...
絶対諦めない！
I'll never give up!
精一杯 精一杯 まだまだ明日を目指して
With all my might, I'll aim for tomorrow.
全力で Do it madamada 夢の向こうへ
Go all out and do it, further beyond the dream.
No way どんな難題でも 最高潮ではじき返せ
No way, no matter the challenge, bounce it back at the peak!
へこたれたって最後まで 全心 全速 3, 2, 1, Define high!
Even if I stumble, I'll go to the end, heart and soul, full speed, 3, 2, 1, Define high!
Run water! どこまでも 僕たちは諦めないからさ
Run water! Everywhere, we'll never give up!
涙 越えていこう ほら、ほら、ほら、今、今、3, 2, 1, Go!
Let's go beyond the tears, look, look, look, now, now, 3, 2, 1, Go!
僕だけじゃない
It's not just me.
君だけじゃない
It's not just you.
悔しくて嫌いになった
I grew to hate it out of frustration.
消えてしまいたいと思った
I wanted to just disappear.
だから聞こえないように叫ぶ歌
So this song is a scream so no one hears.
水たまりに吐き捨ててた 声
A voice spat out into a puddle.
水たまり
作詞・作曲 Carlos.K
Mizutamari
Lyrics & Composition by Carlos.K
この感情は何なんだろう 素直に受け入れられないよ
What is this feeling? I can't accept it honestly.
息もできないほどに押しつぶされてく
I'm being crushed until I can't breathe.
あぁ 誰かの眩しさに焦って 待ってなんて言いづらいなんて
Ah, feeling rushed by someone's radiance, finding it hard to say 'Wait'...
唇を噛み締めた
I bit my lip.
乾いた心に
In my parched heart,
降る雨 想いが溜まる
The falling rain makes my feelings pool.
水面（みなも）に映った
Reflected on the water's surface,
この顔は嘘つきだ
This face is a liar's.
聞いて！
Listen!
嫌いじゃない 嫌いじゃない でも
I don't hate it, I don't hate it, but...
嫌いじゃない 嫌いじゃないでしょ？
You don't hate it, you don't hate it, right?
まっすぐに不器用でもいい
It's fine to be direct, even if awkward.
どうでもいい どうでもいいんだよ
It doesn't matter, it doesn't matter at all.
君を隠すどんな雨も 水たまり踏みつけて
Stomp on the puddles of any rain that tries to hide you.
溢れたっていいんだから
Because it's okay if it overflows
恐れずに前を向いたら 息をして見て
If you look forward without fear, try taking a breath
誰かの物語に生きて 自分が主役じゃないなんて
Living in someone else's story, saying I'm not the lead
分かってるいい子演じるは それでいい
I know that playing the good kid is fine for now
わけないよね 本音は大嫌い
No, it's not. I hate my true feelings.
そんな自分が大嫌い
I hate that part of myself
許せない このままじゃ
I can't forgive it, like this
砂漠に降り注ぐ雨
Rain falling in the desert
傘も差さずに
Without even holding an umbrella
隠した涙は
The tears I hid...
誰にもわからないでしょう
...no one will probably ever know
聞いて
Listen
くだらないくだらない このあらすじは破り捨てたい
Worthless, worthless... I want to tear up this synopsis
書き換える運命を
I'll rewrite my destiny
空っぽなその笑顔に さよならと伝えたんだ
I said goodbye to that empty smile
もうここには戻らない
I'm not coming back here anymore
綺麗じゃない綺麗じゃない でも嫌いじゃない嫌いじゃないでしょう
It's not pretty, it's not pretty, but it's not hated, it's not hated, right?
真っ直ぐに不器用でもいい
It's okay to be straightforward and clumsy
どうでもいいどうでもいいんだよ 君を想うどんな雨も
It doesn't matter, it really doesn't matter, any rain that reminds me of you
水たまり見つけて
Find a puddle
笑われたっていいんだ
It's okay if people laugh at me
溢れたっていいんだから
Because it's okay if it overflows
恐れずに前を向いたら
If you look forward without fear...
息をして見て
...try taking a breath
La la la la...
はい！ということで！
Yes! So!
あー！こよー！
Ah! Koyo!
先輩！歌えたー！
Senpai! We sang it!
ちょっと緊張したかも
I might have been a bit nervous
緊張したー！
I was nervous!
こよも緊張したかもー！
Koyo might have been nervous too!
こよ、お誕生日おめでとう！
Koyo, happy birthday!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
ありがとうございますー！
ということでですね、今回は生演奏パートを 作らせていただいたんですけども
So, this time, we had a live performance part...
こよりは、ミオ先輩のしっとりした歌声が大好きなので、 一緒に歌いたいなと思ってお呼びしちゃいました！
...and because I love Mio-senpai's mellow singing voice, I invited her because I wanted to sing together!
ありがとうー
Thank you
こよのね、可愛い声もさ、なんかいろんな、 かっこいい歌声もあったりさっきも聴いてたんだけど
Koyo's cute voice, and like, various cool singing voices too, I was listening to them earlier.
ありがとうございます、ありがとうございます
Thank you, thank you
いろんななんかこよが見えて、なんか嬉しいなと思ったよ。 歌本当に上手になったよなー
I was happy to see many sides of Koyo. You've really gotten better at singing.
うー、ありがとうございます！ ミオ先輩にそう言ってもらえると嬉しくて泣いちゃうー
Ooh, thank you! I'm so happy to hear that from Mio-senpai, I'm gonna cry!
そしてですね、素敵な演奏は、 Wingさんにしていただいております！
And also, the wonderful accompaniment is provided by Wing-san!
素敵ー！
Wonderful!
すごい！響き渡りますねー
Amazing! It really resonates!
ありがとうございましたー
Thank you very much
はい、ということで、二人で歌うのは...
Yes, so, singing together...
あのフェスのアニマルとか...
...like 'Animal' at that festival...
あとミオ先輩の4周年の『夜もすがら君想ふ』以来ですね
...and it's been since Mio-senpai's 4th anniversary 'Yomosugara Kimi Omou'.
あー、歌ったね、一緒に。エモいね
Ah, we did sing that together. Emotional.
こうやってしっとり、ガチしっとりは初めてかも...
A mellow, seriously mellow performance like this might be the first time...
初めてかもねー
Maybe the first time
ですねー。いや、楽しかったです！ありがとうございます！
Indeed. Wow, that was fun! Thank you!
いや、ちょっとなんか、でもなかなかこういう機会をね、 あの、生演奏でっていうのは...
No, well, opportunities like this, with a live performance...
なかなかないから、ちょっと嬉しかった、でも。 呼んでくれてありがとう
...don't come by often, so I was happy. Thanks for inviting me.
もう今日めちゃくちゃ長時間待たせてるんで...
Since I've made you wait for such a long time today...
いやいやいや、そんなそんな。 嬉しい本当に。忙しい中ありがとうございますー
No, no, not at all. I'm really happy. Thank you for making time in your busy schedule!
こよの誕生日祝えてよかったよ
I'm glad I could celebrate Koyo's birthday.
わー、そして無事に歌えてよかったー！
Wow, and I'm glad we could sing it successfully!
泣かないでー。体調もね、今日整えてきたね、今日ね
Don't cry. You also got your condition ready for today, didn't you?
ホントもう、今日やっと歌えるようになりました、ホントよかった
Really, I finally became able to sing today, I'm so glad.
声もね、出るようになっててすごいなーって
Your voice is coming out well now, it's amazing.
よかったですー！一緒に歌えました、無事に！
I'm glad! We could sing together, successfully!
はい、じゃあまあね、このあとももうちょっと続くみたいだから
Yes, well, it looks like it'll continue a bit longer after this.
うちはここらでちょっとお暇しようかなって思います
So I'll take my leave now.
ありがとうございますー！
Thank you very much!
はい、じゃあ頑張ってね！見守ってるから！じゃあねー！
Yes, so good luck! I'll be watching! See ya!
ありがとう助手君たちもありがとねー！ありがとー！
Thanks, and thanks to the Assistants too! Thank you!
えっさほいさ、えっさほいさ、えっさほいさ...
Essa-hoisa, essa-hoisa, essa-hoisa...
えっほーではないんだ...
It's not "Eh-ho"...
あ、ちょっとだけ水をね...
Ah, just a bit of water...
挑戦して、みんなへの思いを込めた曲です。
This is a song I challenged myself with, filled with my feelings for everyone.
ファーストアルバムから...聴いてください。
From the first album... please listen.
ねぇもしも　ねぇもしも
Hey, what if... Hey, what if...
Dear you 128√e980
作詞：博衣こより　作曲：秋田 涼一
Lyrics: Hakui Koyori / Composition: Akita Yoichi
暗くて孤独に
In the darkness and loneliness...
呑まれそうな夜
...on a night where I feel like I'll be swallowed up
ソファで独り膝抱え
Curled up alone on the sofa
ちっぽけさ感じてた
Feeling so small
強いよね見られがち
I'm often seen as strong
ほんとは弱いのに
Even though I'm actually weak
不器用で負けず嫌い
Clumsy and hating to lose
甘えられないから
Because I don't know how to lean on others
誰にも言えないままの
Remaining unable to tell anyone
ぼくの弱さに
Of this weakness of mine
キミだけが手を差し伸べてくれたんだ
You were the only one who reached out your hand
一緒に笑って
Laughing together
一緒に悔しんで
Feeling frustrated together
そんな日々がかけがえない宝物
Those days are an irreplaceable treasure
一生こんな日が続いていくように
So that days like these will continue forever
ぼくにできることは何だってしたいよ
I want to do anything I can
ねぇもしも　ねぇもしも
Hey, what if... Hey, what if...
キミがぼくを忘れちゃっても
Even if you were to forget about me
キミの中にぼくの生きさまが
If my way of life within you
かすかでも残って
Remains, even just a little
キミがねいるから
Because you are here
強くなれるよ
I can become strong
不安も辛さも一緒なら
If we're together through anxiety and pain
乗り越えられるんだ
I can overcome it all
一緒に泣いて
Crying together
一緒に前を見て
Looking forward together
キミといると嫌いなとこも愛せる
When I'm with you, I can even love the parts of me I hate
一生一緒だよなんて言っても
Even if I say things like "We'll be together forever"
叶うかなんて誰にもわからない　でも
No one knows if it will come true, but...
ねえキミにねぇずっと
Hey, to you... Hey, forever...
好きでいてほしいワガママかな
I want you to love me, is that selfish of me?
すべて夢を叶える日まで
Until the day all my dreams come true
一緒に笑って
Laughing together
一緒に前を見て
Looking forward together
ずっとキミの隣にいられますように
I hope I can stay by your side forever
キミが好きでいてくれるのなら
As long as you continue to love me
ぼくはここにいるよ
I'll be right here
ねぇこれも夢だよ
Hey, this is also a dream
ねえすべて叶うかな
Hey, I wonder if everything will come true
ねえキミにありがとう
Hey, thank you to you
ぱれん　ぱれん　ぱれん
Paren paren paren
輝くんだよ
It's shining!
呼び合う声を合図に
With our voices calling to each other as the signal
パレパレパレ 探しに行く
Parade, parade, parade, let's go search.
スタートは何遍だって
The start is any number of times.
ただ 独り言呟いた
Just muttered a monologue.
ただ 始まりたくて走った
Just wanted to start, so I ran.
遠く暗がりに灯った
Lit up in the distant darkness.
それは眩しすぎた名前
That was a name too dazzling.
それは優しすぎる思い出
Those were memories too kind.
もっと 近づけと手を伸ばした
I reached out to get closer.
重なり合うはず結び合った
Supposed to overlap, we tied together.
ほら 今 内緒は 僕らになった
Look, now the secret became us.
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, it's shining.
悔しさも愛おしさも連れておいで
Bring both regret and preciousness along.
風 夢 羽 飛び立つさ
Wind, dreams, wings, we'll fly away.
ささやかな祈り光 終わりなき始まり
Modest prayer and light, an endless beginning.
君を見つけたこと 胸を張れるよ
I can be proud of finding you.
ここから これから Our Bright Parade Parade
From here, from now on, Our Bright Parade Parade.
まだ 頼りない予感を
An as-yet unreliable premonition.
歌おう 恥ずかしくなんてないよ
Let's sing; there's nothing to be ashamed of.
誰も解けない魔法に
A magic no one can unravel.
いつか また巡り会わしたい
I want to meet it again someday.
あの日 ゼロに始まったストーリー
A story that started from zero that day.
数えきれない言の葉
Countless words.
数えるような思いじゃないさ
Not the kind of feelings you can count.
ほら 今 僕らを ひとつと呼ぼう
Look, now let's call us one.
パレパレパレ 美しいんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, it's beautiful.
ゆらしあえる切なさ 夜はきらめく
Sorrow we can share, the night sparkles.
ハレハレハレ 窓の外
Sunny, sunny, sunny, outside the window.
相応しい旅路とは 君と歩くことさ
The journey that suits us is walking with you.
君と歩くことなんだ
It's walking with you.
「ただいま」も聞けば
If I hear 'I'm home,'
「おかえり」って叫ぶよ
I'll shout 'Welcome back.'
当たり前じゃないか
Isn't it obvious?
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, it's shining.
暗闇を満たすのは 君だ僕だ
It's you and me filling the darkness.
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, it's shining.
悔しさも愛おしさも連れておいで
Bring both regret and preciousness along.
風 夢 羽 飛び立つさ
Wind, dreams, wings, we'll fly away.
ささやかな祈り光 終わりなき始まり
Modest prayer and light, an endless beginning.
君と飛び込んでゆく 素敵なスタートさ
I'll dive in with you; it's a wonderful start.
ここから これから Our Bright Parade Parade
From here, from now on, Our Bright Parade Parade.
告知パートー！
Announcement section!
え、この告知のあとにもまだ歌うので、
Eh, I'll still be singing after these announcements, so...
チャンネルはそのままで最後まで見てってください！
Stay on the channel and watch until the end!
そして、トレンド入りもありがとう！
Also, thank you for making us trend!
なんだかご縁のありそうな方のホームランがすごいです。おめでとうございます！
The home runs from someone who seems to have a connection are amazing. Congratulations!
トレンドもありがとうね！
Thank you for the trend, too!
そしてですね、この告知パート、最後の方に
And then, in this announcement section, towards the end...
こよの配信史上最大の告知もありますので、最後まで見てってください！
There's the biggest announcement in Koyo's streaming history, so please watch until the end!
ではまず一つ目は冒頭でも言っていたこちら！
Now, for the first one, it's this, which I mentioned at the beginning!
博衣こより 1st Album ダウンロード版は0時から販売開始されております！
Hakui Koyori's 1st Album digital version has been on sale since midnight!
概要欄からすでに飛べますのでゲットしてください。1位とかもありがとう！
You can already access it from the description, so please get it. Thank you for reaching 1st place and such!
そしてですね、限定ボーナストラック、はい！はい！はい！はい！こんこよOPが入っているCD...
And then, the limited bonus track, yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! The CD containing the Kon-Koyo OP...
この後、21時からECサイトで受注販売、もう一度行われますよ。
Sales will start again on the EC site from 21:00.
歌詞カードもね、入ってるんで、これじっくり読むのがすごい楽しいとみんなに好評でした。
It includes lyric cards, and everyone said they enjoyed reading them carefully.
そして通常盤封入特典といたしまして、メインジャケットの表情違いのアナザージャケットカードが付いてきます！
And as a regular edition bonus, you'll get an 'another jacket card' with a different expression!
今回も数量限定でこよの直筆サインが入っているかもなので、ぜひまたお手にとってもらえれば嬉しいです！
A limited number might have my autograph, so I'd be happy if you pick one up!
さーて！博衣こより誕生日記念グッズも、出ます！ドーン！
And now! Hakui Koyori's Birthday Celebration goods are also coming out! Boom!
それでは詳細を見ていきましょう。
Let's take a look at the details.
まずは、ももこママに描いていただきました、オリジナルのライブ衣装みたいなすごい可愛いヤツ！
First up, this super cute item with an original live outfit illustrated by Momoko-mama!
これあの架空なんですけど、に、身を包んだこよがライブをしてるよという素敵な2層アクリルパネル！
It's a fictional outfit, but it shows me performing a live—a wonderful 2-layered acrylic panel!
2層になってるんで、なんか遠近感もあって、すごいあの、すごーい可愛いです。語彙力！絶対ゲットしてください。
It's 2-layered, giving it a sense of depth, and it's just... super cute. My vocabulary! Please get it.
そして、はい！フェスで欲しくなったよね、みんな。こよ推しはっぴ！
Next up! You all wanted this at the fes, didn't you? The Koyo-oshi Happi!
ま、ちょっとFes EXPOは一週間前に終わっちゃいましたけれど、ま、次回があるのかもしれませんけれど、何かあるでしょう！
Well, Fes EXPO ended a week ago, but there might be a next time, or something else!
次回のね、ためにぜひゲットしておいて、次の時に着れるようにしておいてください。これ白衣っぽい柄になってて、めちゃくちゃ可愛いです。
Get it for the next time so you're ready to wear it. It has a lab coat-like pattern and is so cute.
そして、次！はい、去年出した制服衣装のとっても可愛いぬいぐるみバッジ！
Next! Yes, the super cute plushie badge of the school uniform outfit from last year!
こちら今までのサイズ感と同じサイズ感になってますよ。くっそ可愛いのでゲットしてください。次！
It's the same size as previous ones. It's incredibly cute, so please get it. Next!
はい、最近ね、あのホロカやってる人も増えてきたので、こんこよカードケース、作ってみました！
Since more people are playing Holo-ka lately, I made a Kon-Koyo card case!
はい、ホロカって結構デッキ枚数が多いので、あの、デッキ全部入るように、あのサイズ大きめに作っております。
Holo-ka decks have a lot of cards, so I made it large enough to fit the entire deck.
え、カードやってないよっていう人もですね、こちら、えー、あの開けてぬいバを挿しとくとか、小物入れとか、色々使えます。
Even if you don't play cards, you can open it and put plushie badges or small items inside.
めっちゃね豪華なね、なんか合皮なのかな？みたいな感じになってますのでゲットしてください。そして、フルセット購入特典はこちら！
It feels very luxurious, like synthetic leather, so please get it. And here are the full set purchase bonuses!
はい、限定です！で、直筆サイン、そして、箔押しサインとメッセージ入りの、えー、ものが付いてきます！
It's limited! It comes with an autograph, and one with a foil-stamped signature and message!
（ポスカードの内容は）博衣よりからのメッセージは届いてからのお楽しみ！
Look forward to the message from Hakui after it arrives!
そして毎年恒例大好評、「君の誕生日を逆にお祝いするよ」というASMRボイスが付いてきます！こちら本当に好評でね、ゲットしてなかった人だいたい後悔してますんで、
And the annual favorite, the ASMR voice where I celebrate *your* birthday, is included! It's so popular that those who didn't get it usually regret it.
自分の誕生日に聴くようにダウンロードしてずっと我慢して自分の誕生日に聴いてください。3月14日の人は1年我慢してください。よろしくお願いします。さらに今回フルセットこちら！
Download it and wait until your birthday to listen. If your birthday is March 14, wait a year. Thank you. Plus, here's more for the full set!
ホロカも付いてきます！可愛い！今回のイラスト可愛すぎてホロカになるの最高すぎないか？
It comes with a Holo-ka! So cute! This illustration is so cute, isn't it amazing it's becoming a card?
推しカード付いてきますよ、推しホロメンカード。ぜひぜひゲットしてくださいね、ホロカ好きの皆様もよろしくお願いします。そしてね、カートオープンが21時5分になるようになってます。
You'll get an oshi card, an oshi holomem card. All Holo-ka fans, please get it. The cart will open at 21:05.
そう、みんなが慌てないように21時5分にカートオープンしますので、配信が終わる前にカートオープンしちゃうかもしれないんですけど、ちょっと余裕あるので、皆さんコメントのURLを要チェックしてください。
Yes, to prevent panic, it opens at 21:05. It might open before the stream ends, but there's time, so check the URL in the comments.
そしてですね、このホロカさんから、なんとここでっていう、映像告知をもらってますので、どうぞ！
And from Holo-ka, I've received a video announcement to show right here. Take a look!
hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME
やったよ助手くん、ついにホロカに、こよが来るやん！
I did it, Assistant-kun! I'm finally coming to Holo-ka!
キリウスユニバース、新ブースターパック、2025年6月20日発売！
Quirius Universe, new booster pack, on sale June 20, 2025!
刮目せよ。
Witness this.
やったよ助手くん、ついにホロカに来るし、なんか、すごいティーザームービーあるよ！
I did it, Assistant-kun! I'm finally coming to Holo-ka, and what a teaser movie!
ということで、なんと、新ブースターパック「キリウスユニバース」が2025年6月20日に発売されるということが、今ここで初めて世の中にでました。速報でいいの？！ここでいいのマジで？！って思いながら、
So, it's just been announced to the world for the first time that the new booster pack 'Quirius Universe' will be released on June 20, 2025. Is this really okay as breaking news?! Here?!
こよちゃんがすごい可愛いカードになってますし、最後にラプ様もいたんで、ラプ様もカード化するんじゃないですかね？詳細は3月18日火曜日の朝7時からの朝こよでさらに詳細情報お届けさせてもらいます。
I've become a super cute card, and since La+ was there at the end, maybe she's getting one too? I'll share more details on Asa-Koyo on Tuesday, March 18, at 7 AM.
カード情報とかもなんか、もらってました確か。なので、お楽しみに！それでは、最後の曲をお届けしたいと思います。
I think I received some card info too. So look forward to it! Now, I'd like to perform the final song.
ファーストアルバムから、キミ＝ラブという、博衣こより初の可愛いEDMをお披露目します！このあと、配信後にMVも公開しますので、このまま飛んでプレミア公開ぜひ見ていってください。
From my first album, I'll perform 'Kimi = Love', my first cute EDM track! The MV will also be released after the stream, so please jump over and watch the premiere.
きてください！
Please come!
そしてMV公開後、メンバーシップ限定生ライブもあります！
And after the MV release, there will also be a membership-exclusive live stream!
歌うし、はいはいも...
I'll be singing, and maybe...
...できちゃうかも！？
...I'll even do some crawling!?
あとね、このアルバムに入ってないオリジナル曲もあるし...
Also, there are original songs not included in this album...
あの、みんなが大好きなあの曲もあるし...
And that song that everyone loves...
まだまだ歌いますよってことで、えー、スクショタイムとかもやるのでぜひ見にきてください！
I'll keep on singing, so I'll also have a screenshot time, so please come and watch!
それでは、聴いてください。
Now, please listen.
キミ＝LOVE。
You = LOVE.
もっと愛して
Love me more
もっと応えてよ
Respond to me more
もっと構って
Pay more attention
溶かしてよ
And melt me away
きっとキミ＝LOVE
Surely You = LOVE
脳内ずっとキミだって
My head's always full of you
問題ずっとダメだって
It's always no good
二進も三進も昼夜逆転
Stuck in every way, day and night reversed
計算中です
I'm calculating
ずっと考えても
Even if I think forever
君のことばっか
It's only about you
ドキドキとトキメキを研究して
Researching the excitement and heartbeats
恋の方程式は
The equation of love
きっと解けるから
Will surely be solved
もっと愛して
Love me more
もっと応えて
Respond more
もっと構って
Pay more attention
この気持ち
To these feelings
もっと知りたい
I want to know more
君のこと...
About you...
I want you 証明！
I want you, proof!
wanchu♪ 回ってアピールで
wanchu♪ Spin and appeal
wanwan♪ 構ってアピールで
wanwan♪ Pay attention appeal
wanchu♪ 回ってアピールで
wanchu♪ Spin and appeal
wanwan♪ 3回転
wanwan♪ Three rotations
wanchu♪ 回ってアピールで
wanchu♪ Spin and appeal
引き寄せて
Draw you closer
ずっとキミ＝LOVE
Always You = LOVE
運命きっとキミだって
Surely destiny is you
数式きっとダメだって
Surely formulas are no good
二進も三進も昼夜逆転
Stuck in every way, day and night reversed
計算中です
I'm calculating
ずっと考えても
Even if I think forever
君のことばっか
It's only about you
可愛いネイル・ヘアメイク研究して
Researching cute nails and hair/makeup
君の心ずっと
Your heart, I wonder
何％か分からない
What percentage I have
好きだよ
I like you
言えたらもっと
If I could say it more
近くなれる？
Could we get closer?
恥ずかしい
Embarrassing
甘えたい
I want to be spoiled
自信ない
No confidence
独り占めしたい
I want you all to myself
嫌われたくない！
I don't want to be hated!
素直になりたい
I want to be honest
重くないかな
I hope I'm not being too heavy
震える心
Trembling heart
それでも伝える
Even so, I'll tell you
だって僕は
Because I...
キミが大好き
Love you
受け止めてね
Please accept it
キミ＝LOVE
You = LOVE
answer 違うの ずっと欲しいのは...
The answer is different, what I've always wanted is...
No.1 なの ずっと欲しいのは
To be No. 1, what I've always wanted is
LOVE の本音
The true feelings of LOVE
wanchu♪ 回ってアピールで
wanchu♪ Spin and appeal
wanwan♪ 構ってアピールで
wanwan♪ Pay attention appeal
wanchu♪ 回ってアピールで
wanchu♪ Spin and appeal
再現性
Reproducibility
wanchu♪ 回ってアピールで
wanchu♪ Spin and appeal
見つけたよ
I found it
I want you 証明！
I want you, proof!
wanchu♪ 回ってアピールで
wanchu♪ Spin and appeal
wanwan♪ 構ってアピールで
wanwan♪ Pay attention appeal
wanchu♪ 回ってアピールで
wanchu♪ Spin and appeal
wanwan♪ 3回転
wanwan♪ Three rotations
wanchu♪ 回ってアピールで
wanchu♪ Spin and appeal
抱きしめて
Embrace me
LOVE が止まらない
LOVE won't stop
このあとMV公開と、メン限ライブ見に来てね！
After this, the MV release and membership-exclusive live, please come watch!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
んー、まっ！ふふふっ
Mwah! Hehehe
画面の前のキミへ
To you in front of the screen
今日は、こよりにとってとても大切なライブを見に来てくれて、ありがとう。
Thank you for coming to watch this live performance, which is very important to Koyori, today.
直前の体調不良で心配かけちゃってごめんね。
I'm sorry for causing worry with my sudden illness right before this.
無事できて、本当によかったです。
I'm so glad it could happen safely.
歌活動の第1歩目なライブと、1stアルバム、どうだったかな？
How were the live concert, my first step in singing activities, and the 1st album?
少しでも君の心をくすぐる何かがあれば嬉しいです。
I'd be happy if there was something that even slightly tugged at your heartstrings.
あたり一面全員助手くんの夢のソロライブに、
To the dream solo live where the whole area is filled with Joshu-kun,
みんなを連れていきたい。
I want to take everyone.
まだまだ1歩目、長い道のりだけど、ついてきてくれるかな？
It's still just the first step on a long journey, but will you come with me?
一緒に歩いていこうね。
Let's walk together.
助手くん、大好きだよ。
Joshu-kun, I love you.
2025年3月15日
March 15, 2025
博衣こより
Hakui Koyori